A Finding Aid to the Francis Patrick Garvan Papers, 1867, 1912-1953, in the Archives of American Art AAA.garvfran
Archives of American Art
- Auction Records, circa 1930-1949; Series 2; 1.75 Linear feet Box 12-13
  2.1: American Art Association, circa 1930-1936
  2.2: Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1946-1949
  2.3: Plaza Art Galleries, 1942-1949
  - American Art Association, circa 1930-1936; 2.1
    - Sales Records, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 14-20)
    - Sales Records, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Sales Records, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Sales Records, 1930s (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1946-1949; 2.2
    This subseries is arranged in rough chronological order with respect to the original arrangement.
    - Catalogues, Books About Books, 1946 April (Box 12, Folder 24-26)
    - Catalogues, Books on Birds, 1946 November (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Sales Records, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Book Sales, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 29-34)
    - Catalogues, Notable American & English Furniture and Decorations, 1947 March (Box 12, Folder 35-38)
    - Catalogues, Pictorial Americana, 1947 April (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Catalogues, American & English Furniture, 1947 April (Box 12, Folder 40-41)
    - Catalogues, American & English Furniture, 1947 May (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Catalogues, Garden Furniture & Sulpture, 1947 June (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Catalogues, English & American Furniture and Old Silver, 1947 September (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Catalogues, Early English & American Furniture and Decorations, 1947 November (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Sales Records, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 7-18)
    - Catalogues, English & American Furniture, 1948 September (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Catalogues, Press Publications, 1948 December (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Sales Records, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 21-24)
    - Catalogues, Notable English Furniture, 1949 March (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Sales Records, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Plaza Art Galleries, 1942-1949; 2.3
    - Catalogues, Currier & Ives Lithographs, 1942 April (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Sales Records, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Catalogues, Oil Paintings, 1942 November (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Sales Records, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Catalogues, American & Continential Oil Paintings, 1946 February (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Catalogues, Furniture, Porcelains, Oriential Rugs, 1946 March (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Catalogues, Furniture, Decorations and Oil Paintings, 1946 May (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Catalogues, Diamond & Gold Jewlery, 1946 May (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Catalogues, Currier and Ives and Audubon Prints, 1946 December (Box 13, Folder 35-37)
    - Sales Records, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Catalogues, Colored Lithographs, 1947 February (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Catalogues, Currier & Ives LIthographs, 1947 April (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Catalogues, Furniture, Decoration, Rugs, and Paintings, 1947 March (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Catalogues, Home Furishings, 1947 November (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Catalogues, Currier & Ives Lithographs, 1947 December (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Sales Records, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 44-46)
    - Sales Records, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Catalogues, Americana, 1948 January (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Catalogues, Furniture, Porcelains, Oil Paintings, 1948 February (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Catalogues, English & American Furnitire, 1948 July (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Sales Records, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 51-52)
    - Catalogues, American Prints, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Sales Records, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Loan Records, 1919-1948; Series 3; 3 Linear feet Boxes 14-16, 46
  Loan records consist of detailed lists and letters Garvan used to track all of the objects he lent to various museums, historic homes, or private individuals.
  - General, 1927-1939; undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Aiken House, circa 1930s (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1929-1938 (Box 14, Folder 3-11)
  - Carlton House, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1935-1936 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Institute, Exhibition Catelogues, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Public Library, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Charleston Museum, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Colonial Dames, 1933-1936 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Corbett, George, circa 1920s (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Cedar Creek Club, 1929-1942 (Box 14, Folder 19-22)
  - Creek Club & Phillips Academy, 1920s-1930s (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Davis, Mrs. John W, 1920s (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Gracie Mansion, 1935-1942 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Greentree Fair, 1931-1937 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Grolier Club, 1929-1936 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Halaey, R. T. H., 1930s (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Hammond Harwood House, 1927-1932 (Box 14, Folder 28-32)
  - Hastings House, 1931-1936 (Box 14, Folder 33-38)
  - Homewood House (Johns Hopkins University), 1931-1943 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Jackson, John, 1934-1936 (Box 14, Folder 40-41)
  - Kamp Kill Kare, 1920s-1930s (Box 14, Folder 42-49)
  - Kaufmann, circa 1931 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Links Club & Anex, 1932-1934 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Long Island Tercentenary Exhibtion, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mary Washington House, 1931-1943 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Memorial Art Gallery, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1926-1929 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Millbrook, 1930s (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1925-1935 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Folk Arts Center, 1935-1938 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Nework Museum, 1930s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Palmer, Mitchell, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Pennsylvania Museum, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
  - Philadelphia Art Aliance, 1936-1942 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Phillips Academy, 1929-1940 (Box 15, Folder 15-19)
  - Phillips Inn, 1928-1948 (Box 15, Folder 20-21)
  - Phillips, John M., 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Philipse Castle, 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 23-24)
  - Private Notesbooks, 1925-1937 (Box 15, Folder 25-29)
  - Racquet Club at Washington, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Reifsnyoer, Howard, circa 1935 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Tapping Reeve House, 1931-1934 (Box 15, Folder 32-33)
  - Thorpe, Russell W., 1927-1937 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Tomilson, John G., 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 35-36)
  - Truesdale, 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Van Cartlandt Museum, 1923-1939 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Webb House, circa 1931 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Wheatley Hills Bank, circa 1928 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Williamsburgh, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Women's National Club, 1929-1932 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Yale, 1928-1932 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
  - Yale, Faculty Club, 1929-1931 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Yale, from Journal, 1929-1931 (Box 16, Folder 4-7)
  - Yale Gallery of Fine Arts, 1931-1932 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - Yale, Silver, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 11-16)
  - Yale, Hammound House, undated (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
  - Yale, Bound Lists, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Yale, Bound Lists, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Yale, Bound Lists, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Yale, Bound Lists, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Yale, Bound Lists, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Oversized Hastings House, from Box 14, Folders 33-38, 1931-1936 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Pennsylvania Museum, from Box 15, Folder 13, 1928-1933 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Estate Records, 1929-1951; Series 4; 0.75 Linear feet Boxes 17, 45
  Estate records include legal records, inventories, correspondence, item tags, and other documentation regarding the management of Garvan's estate. The majority of correspondence in this series belongs to George Corbett, Garvan's business partner and manager of his estate. Included are lists and ledgers complied by Corbett regarding various items in Garvan's collection.
  - Edwin Jackson Fireplace, 1940-1949 (Box 17, Folder 1-7)
  - Estate Documentation, 1931-1939 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Estate Sale, 1937-1941 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Haskell, Elias, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hammerslough, Phillip, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hastings House, circa 1940 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Inventory and Account Records, undated (Box 17, Folder 13-16)
  - Item Tags, 1930s-1940s (Box 45, Folder 11-13)
  - JA Cattle Company, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Mansion House, 1929-1945 (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
  - Mantels, 1940-1945 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Mariners Museum, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 21-22)
  - Montgomery, Charles F., 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Myers, Jerome, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - New York State Museum, 1940-1944 (Box 17, Folder 25-27)
  - Paintings, Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Penzer, Dr. N. M, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Philips, John M., 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Plaza Arts Galleries, 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 31-33)
  - Ridout IV, Orlando, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Silver, Miscellaneous, 1930-1948 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Silverware, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Tiles, Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Yale, 1933-1947 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Inventory, 1928-circa 1940s; Series 5; 26 Linear feet Boxes 17-43
  Inventories document the thousands of pieces of decorative art and artworks Garvan bought and sold as a collector. The first section of this series is a set of inventory lists organized by Garvan's estate. These lists primarily contain the location information of each item; some lists also include price and brief physical description. The second section of the series consists of inventory files with photographs of the object. The files contain more detailed physical descriptions of the items as well as information regarding the style, source, rarity and present location and condition of the objects. These files were originally contained in leather bound binders. Garvan's collection is also documented in inventory cards. The inventory cards range from one-sentence descriptions to containing almost as much information as that found in the inventory files. At some point Garvan adopted a new numbering system for his inventory cards; this series includes both numbered and unnumbered cards.
  - Inventory Lists, Autographed Letters & Documents, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Inventory Lists, Books at 123 64th St., 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
  - Inventory Lists, Books at Westbury Office, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 42-44)
  - Inventory Lists, Ceramics, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Inventory Lists, Coins & Medals, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Inventory Lists, Currier & Ives, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 47-55)
  - Inventory Lists, Currier & Ives, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Inventory Lists, English Art Objects and Antiques, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Inventory Lists, Furniture, circa 1936 (Box 18, Folder 4-6)
  - Inventory Lists, Lincoln Storage Warehouse, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Inventory Lists, Lofts 109-123 W. 64th St., 1936-1940 (Box 18, Folder 8-27)
  - Inventory Lists, Loft at Park Ave., 1935-1938 (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
  - Inventory Lists, Miscellaneous, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 30-36)
  - Inventory Lists, Prints and Paintings, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Inventory Lists, Silver, circa 1928 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Inventory Lists, Trunks & Chests, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Inventory Lists, Wines and Liquors, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Inventory Files, Artists "S", 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 41-44)
  - Inventory Files, Athelets, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Inventory FIles, Beds, 1930s-1940s (Box 18, Folder 46-49)
  - Inventory Files, Bennington Pottery, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - Inventory Files, Birds, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Inventory Files, Bowls, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Inventory Files, Boxes, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 8-10)
  - Inventory Files, Caricatures, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Files, Cellarette, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Inventory Files, Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 13-34)
  - Inventory Files, Chests, 1930s-1940s (Box 19, Folder 35-45)
  - Inventory Files, Clocks, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Inventory Files, Cupboards and Cabinets, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 5-9)
  - Inventory Files, Desks, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 10-14)
  - Inventory Files, Dogs, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Inventory Files, English Pieces, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 16-21)
  - Inventory Files, Etchings and Engravings, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 22-29)
  - Inventory Files, Fireplace Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Inventory Files, Glass, 1930s-1940s (Box 20, Folder 31-48)
  - Inventory Files, Harwood House, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Inventory Files, Highboys and Lowboys, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 3-13)
  - Inventory Files, Historical, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 14-19)
  - Inventory Files, Horse Subjects, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
  - Inventory Files, Mantels, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
  - Inventory Files, Maps, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Inventory Files, Maps of England, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Inventory Files, Marine Prints, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 26-32)
  - Inventory Files, Milbrook, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 33-34)
  - Inventory Files, Mirror, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 35-40)
  - Inventory Files, Miscellaneous, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 41-45)
  - Inventory Files, Moral and Religous, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Inventory Files, Office, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Inventory Files, Paintings, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Inventory Files, Piano, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "A", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "B", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "D", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "E", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "F", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "G", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 9-11)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "H", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "I", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "J", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "K", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "L", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "M", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "N", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "O", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "P", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "R", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "S", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "T", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "V", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Inventory Files, Portraits "W", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 30-33)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "A", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "B", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 35-39)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "C", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 40-42)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "D", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 43-46)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "E", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 47-48)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "F", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "G", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 50-51)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "H", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 52-55)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "I", 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "K", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "L", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "M", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 6-9)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "N", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "O", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "P", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "R", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "S", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 16-18)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "T", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "U", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "V", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "W", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 24-25)
  - Inventory Files, Print Catalogues "Z", 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Inventory Files, Private Notesbooks, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 27-29)
  - Inventory Files, Rural Scenes, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
  - Inventory Files, Screens, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 32-33)
  - Inventory Files, Secretaries and Bookcases, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 34-35)
  - Inventory Files, Settees and Sofas, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 36-41)
  - Inventory Files, Sideboards and Small Tables, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 42-48)
  - Inventory Files, Silver, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 49-53)
  - Inventory Files, Rural Scenes, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Inventory Files, Sporting Prints, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 2-4)
  - Inventory Files, Staffordshire Pottery, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 5-11)
  - Inventory Files, Tables, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 12-30)
  - Inventory Files, Tables Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 31-34)
  - Inventory Files, Trays, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Inventory Files, Unidentified Journal, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 36-37)
  - Inventory Files, Views "A", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 38-39)
  - Inventory Files, Views "B", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 40-41)
  - Inventory Files, Views Colleges and Universities, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 42-44)
  - Inventory Files, Views "C", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 45-46)
  - Inventory Files, Views "D-F", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Inventory Files, Views "G", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Inventory Files, Views "H", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 49-50)
  - Inventory Files, Views Indian Portfolio, 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Inventory Files, Views "I-K", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Inventory Files, Views "L", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Inventory Files, Views "M", 1930s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Inventory Files, Views "N", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  - Inventory Files, Views New York, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 4-9)
  - Inventory Files, Views "M", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Files, Views "O", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Files, Views "P", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 12-15)
  - Inventory Files, Views "Q", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
  - Inventory Files, Views "R", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 18-19)
  - Inventory Files, Views "S", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
  - Inventory Files, Views "T", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 22-24)
  - Inventory Files, Views "V", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Inventory Files, Views "W", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 26-27)
  - Inventory Files, Views "Y", 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Inventory Files, Views, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 29-30)
  - Inventory Files, Western Scenes, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 31-33)
  - Inventory Files, Washstands, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 34-35)
  - Inventory Files, Windsor Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 36-41)
  - Inventory Files, Whitney Gifft Collection, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 42-44)
  - Inventory Files, Working List of Records, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Inventory Files, Yale, 1930s-1940s (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Inventory Cards, 1-20 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Inventory Cards, 21-40 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Inventory Cards, 41-60 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Inventory Cards, 61-80 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Inventory Cards, 81-100 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Cards, 101-120 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Inventory Cards, 121-140 Chairs, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Inventory Cards, 141-160 Lowboys, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Inventory Cards, 161-180 Highboys, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Inventory Cards, 181-200 Highboys and Lowboys, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Cards, 201-220 Desks, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Cards, 221-240 Chests of Drawers, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Inventory Cards, 241-260 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Inventory Cards, 261-280 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Inventory Cards, 281-300 Tables, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Inventory Cards, 301-320 Tables, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Inventory Cards, 321-340 Tables, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Inventory Cards, 341-360 Tables and Cupboards, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Inventory Cards, 361-380 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Inventory Cards, 381-400 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Inventory Cards, 401-420 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Inventory Cards, 421-460 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Inventory Cards, 461-480 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Inventory Cards, 481-500 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Inventory Cards, 501-520 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Inventory Cards, 521-540 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Inventory Cards, 590-600 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Inventory Cards, 601-620 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Cards, 621-640 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Inventory Cards, 641-660 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Inventory Cards, 661-680 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Inventory Cards, 681-700 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Inventory Cards, 701-720 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Cards, 721-740 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Cards, 741-760 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Inventory Cards, 761-780 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Inventory Cards, 781-800 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Inventory Cards, 801-820 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Inventory Cards, 821-840 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Inventory Cards, 841-860 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Inventory Cards, 861-880 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Inventory Cards, 881-900 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Inventory Cards, 901-920 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Inventory Cards, 921-940 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Inventory Cards, 941-960 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Inventory Cards, 961-980 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Inventory Cards, 981-1000 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Inventory Cards, 1001-1020 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Inventory Cards, 1021-1040 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Inventory Cards, 1041-1060 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Inventory Cards, 1061-1080 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Cards, 1080-1100 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Inventory Cards, 1101-1120 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Inventory Cards, 1121-1140 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Inventory Cards, 1141-1160 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Inventory Cards, 1161-1180 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Cards, 1181-1200 Mixed Items, 1930s-1940s (Box 28, Folder 11)